mymmogames.net 2013-04-30

# Privacy Policy - ggFTW MMORPG Community

### Summary

If you only browse ggftw.com (ggFTW), we will only collect information as captured by the server logs. This includes IP address, date/time of access, file/script accessed, and method of access (GET/POST, _etc._ ). This data will be used for internal analytics as well as enforcement of bans/IP blocks and may be surrendered to law enforcement agencies (with a proper subpoena) for investigation of criminal activity. Use of this site constitutes consent to such data collection.

Additionally, ggFTW uses Google Analytics for statistical analysis. You may script block "google-analytics.com" if you do not wish for your access trends to be archived by ggFTW No personally identifiable information is collected during this process and your access trends remain completely anonymous.

By registering an account, you must provide us with an email address and date of birth. ggFTW does not target users under 13 years of age and will not knowingly collect any personally identifiable information from users under 13 years of age. If a user under 13 years of age registers for this site, he or she is in violation of our terms of service and will be banned upon discovery.

If you contribute to the ggFTW wiki or post on the ggFTW forums, every word you post is published in public domain. You have the option, at any time, to remove information you have posted from ggFTW, but the ggFTW staff will not remove information for you. If you want it gone badly enough, you will do the work to remove it. Bear in mind, deleting posts/wiki information does not permanently remove it from our databases.

### Cookies

ggFTW uses cookies to track login sessions. If you do not wish to allow these cookies, you may block them but you will be unable to log in or contribute to ggFTW No personally identifiable information is stored using these cookies.

### Information Sharing

All community text published to ggFTW is published into the public domain and may be freely redistributed, assuming the entity redistributing the information properly cites the source. Exceptions: Guides or other completely original works remain copyright of their authors unless such copyright is surrendered to ggFTW. If information from another site/publication is copied into ggFTW, the source and author (if available) must be noted. Please do not publish copyrighted information without proper authority to publish such information. We will remove all copyrighted information with a substantiated complaint from the copyright holder upon request. Please see our DMCA compliance section in the [site rules](http://ggftw.com/rules) for more information.

All ggFTW exclusive content (articles, reviews) remain copyright of Gavist Media LLC and may not be redistributed without permission.

ggFTW will not sell or share your private information with other entities. If you choose to submit your personal information to a 3rd party ( _i.e._ advertisers), it is your choice and you do so of your own free will.

ggFTW uses some game and publisher images to identify entities, identify specific games, or provide more information on games (such as screenshots, game logos, publisher logos, official wallpapers, or other official creative). These assets are copyrights of the respective publishers or developers with which they are associated.  ggFTW uses these images under fansite licenses, express written permission, or fair use as defined by Title 17, Section 107 of the United States Code.

### User Account Deletion

User accounts will not be disabled, deleted, or removed by the staff at the request of a user. If you no longer wish to be a member of ggFTW, you may simply stop accessing our servers. If you are banned in violation of our rules or Terms of Service, your contributions will not be removed from our databases by the staff. It is your responsibility to ensure you act in compliance with our [rules](http://ggftw.com/rules).
